Good morning, Zenos.
Time to get up.
Good morning, Lily.
I made some black tea.
Thanks.
"A healer is third-rate if
they just heal injuries,
second-rate if they can
wholly heal a person,
and first-rate if they can
make the world a better place."
This is the Kingdom of Herzeth, a nation
whose history is intertwined with healers.
The contributions of
healers helped it expand
and gained it a position of real importance.
The royal hospital is
where many healers gather
to learn more sophisticated healing magic
and earn their license before
beginning their journeys as healers.
But in a corner of the kingdom, there's
someone who didn't receive a formal education
and doesn't have a license
to practice healing.
Thanks again, man.
Here's some cash.
Don't worry about it.
I'm always willing to heal if
you're willing to pay the price.
Thanks again!
That was great, Zenos.
You've got a house call today, right?
Yeah. I'll be back before nightfall.
Okay! I'll be ready and
waiting with dinner by then.
Have a safe trip!
I'm heading out.
Oh, Carmilla! Dinner isn't ready yet.
Let's have a look...
Stew, eh? I always look forward
to your cooking, Lily!
Leave it to me! 'Cuz I'm gonna
be Zenos's wife someday!
I can always cook something tasty!
Such a hard worker.
I believe I'll rest in my room for now, though.
Doc?
I'm here to visit.
Huh? Is he not in?
Zophia, Zenos is off on a house call.
Seriously?
I guess I'll wait until he gets back, then.
I was hoping to have him to
myself by showing up early...
I figured you'd show.
Sir Zenos! Lynga has come to see you.
No one's around...
Zenos is on a house call.
Hey.
Lynga was going to lick Sir Zenos
all over while he fluffed my tail...
I'm already waiting for Doc to get
back, so how about you run on home?
Lynga will be the one waiting.
I actually live here!
Guess you're right!
She's here, too.
Zenos! I've come for amusement.
Where are you?
Loewe, Zenos is on a house call.
The others are inside.
You can join us, but only after fixing the door.
The whole gang's here, I see.
You all copy Lynga.
Let me guess: you both found the promise
of Lily's cooking irresistible?
No, that's just you.
And now the secret ingredient...
We'll be eating when Zenos gets back.
Are you all going to join us?
That was my intention.
Since I'm here, I might as well.
Of course, Lynga will eat, too!
I'm looking forward to a group meal.
But I'd better put the laundry away.
Watch the pot, okay?
Whatever it is, it smells good.
I can't wait until dinner!
I was thinking the same thing.
Let's have a quick taste while it's still hot.
This is amazing!
Lynga, too!
This isn't sneaking a bite. Just a taste test!
I can't stop.
Unbelievable... Lily is gonna
be pissed at you two.
That was Lynga's!
Maybe just a sample, so I can learn
how the doc likes his food seasoned...
I hope Zenos gets back early.
Well, this is a real mess
we've gotten ourselves into.
Lynga agrees.
My stomach can attest to that.
You two ate it all!
Exactly! You two are unbelievable.
Do you girls have amnesia or something?
Oh, good idea! Lynga remembers nothing!
I get it! We can just make more!
So that's your plan, eh?
I guess I'm in, then.
Let's fill this pot up with ingredients.
Would any of you care to
explain what happened?
Zophia. Lynga. Loewe.
It's actually a complicated story...
Lynga doesn't know.
I'm not sure myself.
I'm not sure I heard that right.
One more time: please explain what happened.
It smelled so good, I wanted to taste it...
Lynga's hands moved on their own.
It was very good!
Great, now she's upset because of you two.
Loewe eat too much!
It was so good, I couldn't stop!
Don't blame the food.
I nearly ate the whole pot...
That can't be good for digestion.
I could always have Zenos
check me out after.
Don't waste Doc's time with
that kind of nonsense.
The fur on Lynga's tail is feeling rough,
so I need Zenos to rub it like usual.
Quit sharing your delusions with us.
Zophia, jealousy is not becoming.
Maybe instead of Lynga, you should be
envious of this honed body of steel?
Sir Zenos wouldn't like a bulgy mess!
He likes Lynga's double serving of
athletic slenderness and fluffy goodness!
You two are getting way off track.
Loser lizard is chirping again.
You got something to say, pup?
Don't leave me out.
Stay out of it.
Everyone...
If you start fighting, Zenos will be mad.
I was really hoping we
could all eat together.
I'm sorry, Lily.
Sorry! Lynga will help make dinner!
You'll have my aid, too.
I can handle heavier tasks!
We only had enough ingredients
to make that one batch...
Nothing else.
Excuse me?
So sorry!
I was so looking forward to eating the
stew Lily made... and you ate it all?
Whatever should I do about that?
Maybe I'll see what a soul that's
been flavored with stew tastes like?
You two, apologize!
We're so sorry!
Ingredients...
I need you all to bring me more ingredients.
Lynga will get what you need!
Consider it done!
I'll get you the real good stuff!
I can get as much as you need!
That was the last of the herbs, too...
Shouldn't you have been angrier with them?
I'm not that mad.
You're certainly forgiving, Lily.
If they had gotten into my
liquor as well as the food,
they'd have all been cursed.
It's because I'm a grown-up!
Plus, I like it when we're all together.
I wonder if I'll be able to finish
dinner by the time Zenos gets back...
Unbelievable. Just what are you doing?
What am I going to do with you?
Where have you been?
M-My stomach hurt, so I went to a hospital,
but I didn't have any money,
so they wouldn't see me...
Do you really think a stomachache is enough
to get you a reprieve? You, a slave?
Ridiculous. Back to work with you.
I-I'm so sorry!
A grimy grave like this is perfectly
suited to a grimy demihuman.
This is pathetic. On your feet already!
For you to give me all this trouble...
Do you want to be in one of these graves?!
That's enough loafing around.
Hurry and find anything of value.
You can't even talk anymore?
Absolutely worthless.
I'll be heading back now.
You will be fed today... if you earn it.
Blood?
What are you doing?!
Damn it. What is going on here?
You there!
My slave has gone mad and
started attacking me!
Can you do something?!
What are you talking about?
Kind of self-absorbed, aren't you?
She's caught up with me! That's her!
What were you doing?
Just our usual work.
What work is that?
A bit of farming, that's all.
Now, look at these wounds!
I need to get to a hospital
as soon as possible!
If you can do something
about her, I'll pay you!
What's wrong?
That was rather violent.
You feeling all right?
Quite impressive...
Now do away with her!
That's not happening.
Why?
My job isn't killing people.
If you insist on that kind of nonsense,
you could get me—an aristocrat—killed!
She's just a slave! I can
always buy a new one!
Sorry, but I try to save any lives I can.
And who do you think you are?
A healer.
What kind of healer can do that?!
She's fast. Faster than your
average demihuman should be.
I'll get you up in a second.
Just calm down for me.
No, no, no...
It hurts...
I can't... anymore...
That explains it.
I've heard of dinner and conversation,
but dinner and possession is new.
I'll take care of you now. Heal.
I wonder what kind of "farming"
gets you possessed by ghosts.
This takes care of today's work, though.
Her broken leg was healed in an instant.
He's incredibly powerful!
Y-You there... You're actually a healer.
Yeah, I am.
Th-Then save me!
I'm off the clock for today, actually.
Can you hold out until tomorrow?
Tomorrow? I'll die by then!
Heal me right now!
Right now, huh?
It'll cost you a bit extra. Is that all right?
That should more than suffice.
Whoa.
That's nowhere near enough.
Th-That's not enough?!
But it's already more than the market price!
Do you really think a healer can fleece
someone with such extravagant costs?!
Well, I'm an underground healer
without a license, so...
Underground healer? Such a thing exists?
It's an underworld gig.
Kind of like grave-robbing.
Grave-robbing? Whatever do you mean?
Oh, right, "farming."
In that case...
I'll take her to make up the difference.
Her? The slave?
Do what you will with her!
All right, you've got a deal.
That's your payment taken care of.
Bloody job's not worth the trouble...
You awake?
Ow...
Who are you?
I'm Zenos.
I bought you.
How's your name pronounced?
I'm Til.
You... bought me?
Yeah. Now strip, Til.
You cost a lot.
I've gotta make sure
you're in good condition.
Right...
I knew it.
There's a gallstone blocking your
bile duct, causing inflammation.
You were hunched over as
if you had abdominal pain.
That and the jaundice caught
my interest, so I followed you.
I'll fix you right up.
What just happened?
What do you mean?
I opened you up, took the stone
out, and closed you back up.
No incantation, no magic circle...
No trace of an opening, either!
Any healer could pull that off.
You can do all that, Master?!
It's just normal.
No, it's not!
Thank you for curing me.
I don't know how to thank you...
You really think thanks are enough?
What I want is an equal price.
That means it's time for you to get to work.
Wh-Whatever you want!
I'll pay you back as your slave!
Ask... whatever you want.
Could you show me where to find this?
Or not?
I-I can.
Right this way, please.
Is this right?
It sure is.
Thanks, Til.
Thanks aren't necessary.
But is this really all you need?
I was anticipating... a lot more.
And I'm willing to...
Nah, you did your job.
What do you mean?
Just what I said.
But, Master, I'm indebted to you!
And like I said, you paid me back.
I always demand a fair
price for the labor I do,
and I always pay a fair price
for what I expect others to do.
I haven't done anything yet.
You found the leaves.
Leaves I couldn't have found on my own.
B-But those are just...
Point is, their value is equal
to what I did for you.
All debts are settled.
Your life's your own now.
My life is... my own?
What... I would like to do now is...
I don't really know.
But now that I'm not a slave,
I'm going to live to find out!
And when I do find out,
I'll come and tell you!
Is that all right, Zenos?
Sure.
See you around, Til.
If you get hurt, come and see me.
I can take care of you
as an underground healer.
But not for free, of course.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Zenos.
D-Dinner's not ready yet...
Zenos!
Sir Zenos!
Doc!
What are you three doing here?
Maybe don't ask, okay?
Lynga didn't do anything wrong.
I assure you, I did not sneak any food!
Vegetables, fish, and lots of meat!
I gotta make the most of all this!
You seem to have had some fun.
Didn't see you up there.
Well, well, is that a new
girl I sense you've met?
Quit poking fun.
Since everyone brought so much,
I can make a whole bunch of food!
Yeah? Sounds good.
Just you wait!
I'll make some black tea first,
and we can drink it together!
Sure.
The Underground Healer in
the Abandoned Part of Town
"The Underground Healer in
the Abandoned Part of Town."